[Dustin] And then I got in the car
to come here,
and I'm putting on my seat belt,
and I hear my shoulder pop.
I mean, I hear my body making
bad noises all day.
-[Dr. Powell] Well, you're getting older.
-Yeah. I'm getting older.
[sighs] It's got me thinking that, um...
I don't know, when I'm on my death bed
and someone is deciding to pull the plug,
I want it to be my kid,
not my pool guy, you know?
Not that I have a pool, but...
"My kid."
Did you notice
that you just said "my kid"?
[chuckles] Well, yeah, I mean, I...
[inhales sharply]
I've been thinking lately
that maybe I want to start a family.
What exactly is going on between you
and Mickey right now?
-How is it?
-Great.
I mean...
obviously things went bad
the first time around, but...
I don't know. Feels different this time.
I like hearing this.
It's what I've been drilling here.
You deserve to be happy.
You... you need to feel entitled
to your own happiness.
Yeah.
No, definitely. I'm...
I am entitled to be
in a relationship with Mickey.
I mean, that's what I want.
I can't fuck this up again.
Okay. Well, that's your time.
-And I'm gonna see you next week, okay?
-Okay.
Just a little FYI.
I'm having this mindfulness retreat
at Esalen next month.
No pressure, but if you and Mickey felt
that it would be, uh,
valuable to you two...
[stutters] I'll run it by her.
Uh, the meals are included in the price.
[theme music playing]
We need to change the music
on this show.
I mean, every time we do a serious moment,
they play violins.
It makes me want to claw
my fucking ears off.
Okay, Mickey. Can I just do this?
Whoo! I just talked to Business Affairs
and Stella's deal is closed.
So, she is officially part
of the Gravity Subzero family. [chuckles]
Wow! That's...
Wow, that's cool. [chuckles]
You made our asses look good.
That's 'cause I'm hot shit.
Well, your hot shit came out of
our lame asses. [laughs]
[Dr. Greg chuckles softly]
I just wanted to give you the good news.
And, so, later, just swing by my office,
okay? Yes!
Well...
congrats, Mickey. [chuckles]
Thanks. I know you don't mean that,
but, whatever.
No, I do. Seriously.
Bravo.
Thank you. I, uh, appreciate that. Um...
That's... that's nice.
It's funny, huh?
Sometimes it's hard for us
to accept a compliment, right?
I'm wired the same way, too.
Yeah, I don't know. It's hard to accept
a pat on the back at work,
when you're shitting the bed
in the rest of your life.
-Oh.
-[sighs]
What's wrong? Something up?
-Oh, like I would ever tell you.
-Oh, come on.
[stutters] Look, I know
that we used to clash, but...
remember how we used to get along?
You know, I'd really things to go back
to being like that.
Supportive, kind.
You know, really...
really there for each other.
Okay, um...
Well, Gus went out of town for work,
and it was really hard.
And then I started seeing an ex...
and then he got super clingy,
and now, Gus is back in town
and I don't know what to do.
Wow. That's a...
a lot to unpack there. Hmm?
Yeah.
So, what do you think?
Do you have any advice?
Oh, I don't really have any advice.
I don't know what I could give.
You're a fucking nightmare. [chuckles]
-Excuse me?
-I'm sorry, no.
[stutters] I didn't mean it
to come out that way.
-Uh, just, please go.
-Yeah.
But, hey. Maybe it's a good thing
that we said it out loud.
You said it.
Yeah. But... now it's out there.
So, you can address it. [chuckles softly]
Excuse me, I'm gonna go get a donut.
[chuckles nervously]
But seriously, [stutters]
I still want you to talk to me if you...
Right.
[Chris] Hey, everybody listen up!
-Cruikshank's back, motherfucker!
-[all cheer]
Whoo!
Hey!
-All right, hey, guys. Oh. I'll do it.
-Gus, my boy!
Put it down. Let's get a picture.
-Chris! Come on, get a picture with us.
-[Chris] All right, all right.
-A group pic on three. One, two, three...
-[camera clicks]
[Gus] And four.
[all singing]
♪ They say that the cider house sucks ♪
♪ But they're all fools ♪
♪ 'Cause what they don't know is
The cider house rocks ♪
♪ And the cider house rules ♪
One more time.
How are you, dude?
How was working on, uh, Liberty Is Free?
-Oh, Liberty Down.
-Yeah.
Yeah. It was, uh... It was okay.
You know, it's just a little tough
being away from home.
-Being away from Mickey.
-Ah...
Bertie said Mickey was having
a hard time with it, too.
-Oh, she said that?
-Yeah.
Yeah, well, I don't know.
I mean, at first...
[inhales sharply] At first, it was fine.
-We were talking every day.
-Uh-huh.
-It was going well.
-Mmm-hmm.
And then, by the end there,
we weren't, like, talking at all.
-Oh, man...
-And I started...
getting the vibe of, like,
"Oh, she's not into this anymore,
and she wants it to be over."
But then, last night she texted me,
and wanted to see if I wanted
to hang out tomorrow, so...
-Yeah. Yeah.
-Awesome.
I don't want to, like,
pat myself on the back here too hard.
But those last few days in Atlanta,
you know, I just... I took a step back,
and I gave her her space.
And I think that's, like, why she's
texting me now, you know? It worked.
Yeah, me and Bertie
were kind of like the same thing.
Like, we broke up,
and I was home crying all the time.
And then I didn't call her
'cause I was gonna kill myself.
She thought that I was giving her space.
-Mmm-hmm.
-So, she got back with me.
Oh, look at us, man.
We are, like, killing it.
-Yeah.
All right, well,
I'm gonna get back to this party.
You can stay here if you like.
[grunts] Nice and comfy.
Yeah. The coats are comfy.
Hey, Gus.
If I borrowed, like, $100 from you,
I could pay you back $110 later on.
-If you were cool with that.
-Oh. Yeah, maybe.
Or, you know what, I'm trying to sell
my Nintendo 64, if you're interested.
-Let's talk about it later.
-Okay.
-Get back to this party. Okay.
-Cool.
[sighs]
[Frank] Adiós, amigo.
-Bye-bye. See you.
-You gotta drop by our place again.
We got some new speakers,
and I'm serious,
you put on Houses of the Holy, right,
and it sounds like Zep's playing
in your living room.
Wow.
-Well, sign me up. I... I'll be by soon.
-[Frank] We gotta go.
Getting out of here, too, man.
Okay, Kev, and uh, hey, now that
I'm back in town, we gotta hang out.
-For sure.
-Yeah, I'm gonna turn this
work friendship into a real friendship.
There's nothing you can do about it.
Sorry.
It's all good.
I already knew we were friends.
Ever since you started coming
to the snack table
-when you didn't want somethin'.
-Yeah, that's a telltale sign.
-I knew what was up.
-Yeah, you knew.
-All right. Bye, buddy.
-See you soon, man.
Oh, Gus. I forgot to tell you.
We saw your little sweetheart
the other day.
-That's right.
-[Gus] You did?
-Yeah, she was out hiking with her friend.
-Wait. Mickey was hiking?
-[Wade] Yeah.
-With what friend?
-Shaun or...
-No, it was some guy.
-Was a dude.
-Some guy?
-[Chris] All right. Let me at him!
-Hey!
-Welcome back, man.
-[Wade] Love you, man.
[Gus] Hey, guys. Thanks for coming over.
-It was good to see you.
-Great to see you. I'm glad you're back.
-I appreciate it.
-See you.
-Let me know about that Nintendo 64.
-Sure.
-Yeah, yeah. Okay. Bye.
-[Beth] Bye!
[chuckles]
[cell phone chimes]
[Mickey] Hey!
Hey.
You look tan.
-Really? Do I?
-Uh... I don't know.
Feel like that's what people say
when someone comes back from a trip.
Well, then,
let's just say I look super tan.
Hey.
-You want to order something?
-Sure. Yeah.
So, how have you been?
Good. Good to be back. Yeah.
-How about you? How are you?
-Good. Good. Yeah.
[scatting]
Things got, uh... pretty crazy
between the two of us there.
Yeah, I know.
Time apart can really, uh,
fuck up a relationship.
I mean, that's what happened
to my best friends, Katy and Russell.
Who?
Oh, did I not tell you?
My best friends are Katy Perry
and Russell Brand?
-No, you never mentioned that.
-Yeah, yeah. They're good kids.
-[man] How's it going?
-Hey.
Can I get, um, a soy latte?
And I will take a ordinary latte.
-Ha! I got it.
-Thank you.
Ah. Thanks, Mickey.
And, hey, I just want to say,
you know, as far as us being apart, I...
I know I could have handled things better.
I was way out of line there.
-It's fine, whatever.
-No, Mickey.
I'm serious.
You're right. I am very codependent.
And it's scary for me
to look at my own shit,
so I focus on yours 'cause it's easier,
and that's just super unfair to you,
and...
I am sorry.
I... I appreciate that. Thank you.
Yeah. I just... I don't know, I gotta...
try my best,
just look at my own shit, you know?
-Well, Al-Anon can help with that.
-Hmm.
Yeah. Well, I've actually gone
to a few meetings, so...
What? Really?
Gus, that's amazing. I'm so proud of you.
-Ah.
-Um, I'm sorry. That was condescending.
No. No, no. Not at all.
-[man] There you go.
-Hey.
[Mickey] Really? You've never?
I'm serious. I've never had a wet dream.
-Oh, my God.
-It's weird. I know.
-[cell phone vibrating]
-I don't know why. [chuckles]
Oh.
You can reply to that if you need to.
It's cool.
-It's fine. Yeah.
-You sure? Okay.
Do you have any, uh, plans today?
What are your Saturday plans?
I'm doing the laundry.
I am paying my bills.
I'm going to the post office.
Just some... real exciting shit, Mickey.
Hmm. Well, maybe you could come by
my place later? Like, 9:00 or 10:00?
Yeah. Sure.
I'm glad you're back. I missed you.
I missed you, too.
Hey, remember that time I went to Atlanta
and we both flipped out?
-Oh... such fond memories.
-[chuckles]
-[Dustin] You gotta taste this sauce.
-[Mickey] What?
Taste this sauce I made. It is amazing.
Mmm. That was really hot.
Oh, sorry, should've warned you.
But it's good, right?
I am killing it with sauces lately.
Yeah, it's good.
Yeah, but you taste better.
Mmm, thank you.
What's wrong? You're acting weird.
I don't think we should do this anymore.
Do what?
You and me. All of it.
It's moving...
too fast.
It's getting too serious,
and I'm not ready for it.
I think we should break it off.
[clicks tongue]
I guess we should.
Okay, uh, I'm gonna go.
I guess you are.
-All right, take care.
-I will take care.
Are you okay? 'Cause you, like, seem okay,
but, like, scary okay.
-You should go now.
-[pot clangs]
[softly] Okay. All right.
Is this because that guy is back in town?
The little tree sprite?
The one at the Springwood? Gus?
No! This has nothing to do with him.
Yeah, that guy will...
never make you happy.
But I guess you want to be unhappy.
Okay, yeah, you've got me all figured out.
-Goodbye, Dustin.
-Goodbye, whore!
See? There it goes!
You called me a whore again.
You are the same. This is all the same.
[door opens and slams]
[exhales]
[sighs]
[music playing faintly over speakers]
Bertie, I'm sorry for putting you
in an awkward situation with Dustin.
That really was not fair of me.
Oh, okay. I'm not mad anymore.
I spoke to my mom about it, and she said,
"Bertie, you're judging Mickey."
And my mom's right.
And who am I to judge?
I'm hooking back up with Randy again.
I mean, what the fuck am I doing?
He only could pay me back 'cause
he borrowed more money from his family.
He's really excited
about his new job at the moment,
which is being in the background
of a TV show.
He's in his 30s.
Also, he loves it
because he gets to lie on a gurney
during his lunch hour.
-[chuckles]
-What am I doing?
Why did I go back?
They say that you go back
to painful situations
because they're comfortable and familiar.
I hear that.
Sometimes when I'm in pain, I'm like,
"Hello, old friend."
Yeah. I'm very comfortable with pain.
It's the happy part I'm not used to.
Right. We need to get comfortable
with the happy part.
-Yeah.
-Definitely.
-Do you want the rest of this yogurt?
-No...
All right, then.
It's goin' back in the fridge.
Hey, Bertie, Gus is coming over tonight,
if you can handle that.
Oh... sure.
I mean... I definitely won't tell him
about Dustin,
but I should probably tell you,
I've been told I'm a terrible liar.
I mean, I don't think so.
I think I'm quite convincing,
but people have told me
I'm really very bad at it.
Well, I ended things with Dustin today,
-if that makes it any easier.
-Really?
How did that go down?
You know how some guys when they're angry
are like, tick, tick... boom?
Dustin's like tick, boom!
You should've seen the look in his eye.
I mean...
I didn't know
if I was gonna get out of there alive.
Right. Are you gonna tell Gus
about any of this?
No! Jesus, that would just hurt him.
What if he asks?
If he asks me if I've slept
with anybody else, then I will say yes.
I'm not gonna lie.
But I wasn't really
breaking the rules or whatever.
Huh. Okay.
[knock on door]
-Hi! [chuckles]
-Hey, hey!
-Hi, Mickey.
-Hi.
-Hey!
-Hey, great to see you!
It's good to see you, too. How are you?
Gus, the craziest thing happened
at work today.
You won't even believe it.
There was this man, and he ate so many
Steak-umms, and he threw up everywhere,
but then he still was like, "I love 'em!"
[chuckles] It was so stupid.
-Oh, that's, uh...
-It was crazy!
-I can see how that's funny.
-I'm gonna text my mom about it.
Okay. Good to see ya.
Ooh, that's a nasty little stain there.
-Oh, yeah, it's wine. [sighs]
-Oh.
I wasn't drinking.
Okay, I wasn't saying anything.
No, it was Bertie.
She had a full glass of wine
and stubbed her toe on the coffee table
and it just spilled.
It's all good. I don't care.
[Mickey moans softly]
-[Gus grunts]
-[sighs]
I'm sorry that I acted so shitty
when we were apart.
-I--
-It's okay. Don't--
-No, I feel--
-I... I was...
making you that way. It's fine.
I think it's, like I said,
I'm really bad with separation, and...
it made me act out and I'm...
I'm sorry. I think I'm...
way more into you than I even know.
Aw.
Well, me, too.
I mean, I'm into you, not me.
-Or... you get it.
-Hey, hey, I have a question for you.
What? What?
What do you always wanna do in bed,
but you're too nervous to ask for?
Oh, uh... I don't know.
Okay, well,
what have you always wanted to do,
but you've never done?
'Cause I wanna do that.
Oh, my God. That's so much pressure.
That's like one of those things
I wish I had an answer for.
You in your mind imagine,
"Oh, I hope somebody asks me
this question."
But I... I don't know.
I don't like talking...
[inhales deeply] about sex.
I'm up for anything in the moment, Mickey.
What if I, like, put a finger up your ass?
-Uh, maybe.
-Yeah?
Yeah, just don't give me
a heads-up beforehand.
It's like, I don't wanna know
the end of a movie before it happens.
May I feel free to make a bold choice?
-Yes. [chuckles]
-Okay.
Make a bold choice.
[yawns]
-Good morning.
-[inhales deeply]
[grunts softly] Good morning.
[cell phone vibrating]
[Mickey] Sounds like my phone's
blowing up. Can you hand it to me?
[inhales deeply]
-[grunts] Okay.
-[cell phone continues vibrating]
Hey. [clears throat]
Gus-Gus, let's get out of here.
Really? We just woke up.
I know, but I'm feelin' antsy.
Let's get out of here.
Let's do something fun.
Mmm.
-Look at you.
-What are you doing?
-I want to take your picture.
-No.
-What?
-Morning photos are really nasty.
-Are you serious?
-Yeah.
Morning photos are the best.
You got messed up hair, little puffy eyes.
People are at their cutest in the morning.
-I'm serious.
-I love it. What?
Let's go do something.
What do you wanna do?
You know what I always thought
could be fun?
Uh, at the park they have, uh...
They have paddleboating.
Perfect. Yeah, let's do it.
-You wanna paddleboat?
-Mmm-hmm.
Okay.
Um...
-I gotta piss first.
-Okay.
-Quick piss.
-[groaning]
-Come on, Gus. I'm serious.
Okay, okay.
Oh, fuck.
I thought you weren't
a morning person either.
That's why I like you.
-[sighs]
-But you're... Okay, okay.
[cell phone vibrating]
[softly] Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
[Gus] All right. Initiating paddleboat.
Five, four...
three, two...
Fun?
[knocking on door]
-Hey.
-Oh, hey, Dustin. How are you?
-I'm well. How are you?
-I'm good.
-Oh, do... Come in!
-Thanks.
-Uh, is Mickey here?
-Uh, no.
No. She... she stepped out.
Okay. Do you know where she went?
Is she coming back soon?
No.
I don't know. She didn't say.
Don't know.
Okay. Just, uh, tell her I dropped by?
Or, you know, don't worry about it.
You know what? Let her know.
-Okay. I'll give her the message.
-Okay.
-Uh, also, I think I left a jacket here?
-Oh, I haven't seen one.
What does it look like?
Uh, it's like a letterman's jacket
type thing.
-Cool.
-I may have left it in Mickey's room.
Would you mind checking?
I would go in there,
I just don't wanna root around
in her stuff when she's not here.
Oh, okay, sure. I'll go have a look.
Thank you.
[Bertie] What color is it?
Uh, it's black and gold.
[Bertie] That sounds nice.
Sorry, Dustin, I've looked everywhere.
-There's no sign of it. Sorry.
-No sign of it?
Okay, no worries.
I'll keep looking for it.
It'll turn up somewhere.
I will, uh, see you around.
-[Bertie] Okay.
-Thanks again.
Weird.
So, yeah, I guess, like, a few years ago,
they drained this lake,
and everybody was expecting
to find all these dead bodies.
But then when they did it,
there were no dead bodies,
and everybody was weirdly disappointed.
[chuckles]
Glad you're back.
Aw. I'm glad I'm back, too.
[inhales deeply] It feels good.
[Gus] You know what's cool?
We both have the names
of Disney mice, right?
'Cause I'm Gus-Gus from Cinderella,
you're Mickey, as in the classic mouse.
-Mickey Mouse, yeah.
-Yeah.
You like being reminded of that
-I'm sure, right?
-Mmm-hmm.
[Gus] Oh, cool.
Uh, you know what?
Can we get some broccoli?
'Cause I really, um...
I'm just feeling
like I need more broccoli.
And I also really have to go
to the bathroom,
so maybe you can get the broccoli,
-and I'll meet you--
-Are you okay?
-[Mickey] Yeah.
-[Gus] You seem jumpy.
[Mickey] Ugh, when I gotta pee I'm...
Um...
Ask a lot of questions, make sure
you don't get, uh, ripped off, okay?
[man] Fresh strawberries!
Papayas! Oranges!
Lemon! Grapefruit! We got melons!
-Pineapple?
-Sorry, hi.
[man] Oh.
[whispers] Gus! Gus, hi.
Hey, how's it going?
Hey, I got your broccoli.
I haggled him down to $1,000.
I think that's fair, right?
Yeah, you want to get out of here?
I'm having a good time.
You want to check out a few more booths
-and then maybe head home?
-Uh...
Yeah, um,
how about I get you a massage?
-I don't know. I don't need it.
-Come on!
You got me broccoli.
I'll get you a massage.
-Okay.
-Yeah, I'm getting that for you.
-What? Wow. Thanks.
-Mmm-hmm. Yeah.
[Gus] That actually would be amazing
right now.
Hey!
-Hey, would you like some strawberries?
-Uh, no. No, thank you.
[girls screaming and laughing]
[man] You're a little tense in here.
[Gus] Yeah,
I get really tense in my neck.
-[man] Wow.
-[Gus] Yeah.
-[man] Do you work out a lot?
-[chuckles]
-[Gus] No. [chuckles]
-Really?
-Construction work?
-[Gus] You flatter me.
[man] Pressure point for all--
Hey. Okay, uh, you ready to go?
-Here you go.
-Huh?
We just started.
-It's hot. Feels like I'm gonna pass out.
-Yeah, sorry. Okay.
-Thanks, so much.
-Mickey, this is Kent, by the way.
[man] What the...
No!
-[Gus exhales] Ooh.
-[sighs] Oh, my God.
It feels so good to be back inside.
Sorry I was acting so weird back there.
When I'm out in the sun for too long,
it kinda fries my brain.
Oh, totally understand. It's all good.
You don't have to convince me
that the indoors are always better
than the outdoors.
You know... I'm gonna get a soda
from the vending machine.
-You want anything?
-Yeah, anything. Surprise me.
All right, I will BRB.
That's how the cool kids say
"be right back."
[sighs]
[Dustin] Excuse me,
do you know Gus Cruikshank?
Hey, uh, [clears throat]
do you know my buddy Gus Cruikshank?
-Who?
-Yeah.
Do you guys know Gus Cruikshank
by any chance?
All I'm saying is, you could've given us
a bigger heads up on this gray paint.
That's, like, your one job
on the committee council.
We put fliers announcing the change
in everyone's mailbox.
Well, I'm sorry, but I didn't get one,
and I'm not okay with the change.
-Gray is sad.
-Gray is sophisticated, elegant and cool.
Excuse me,
either of you know Gus Cruikshank?
-Yeah, he's my buddy.
-Great.
We were just at the farmers market
with Mickey.
I know Mickey, too. Great girl!
-Yeah. My phone died.
-[Chris] Huh.
And I don't know where Gus' place is.
I'm pretty sure they came back here.
Oh, yeah, this happens all the time.
Gus is over in Building E. Second floor.
I want to say E-232.
Two-thirty-two. Great.
Thanks. Appreciate it.
No problem. Happy to help, amigo!
[knocking on door]
All right, cool your jets.
[knocking continues]
Is he here?
-Fuck, dude!
-We need to talk.
No, we do not need to talk.
I'm not leaving until we talk!
Okay, all right.
Okay.
[lock clicks]
Dude, what the fuck is going on with you?
You're chasing me around a farmers market?
You're stalking me?
I am doing what I didn't do last time.
I'm fighting for you.
Well, don't. I don't want you to.
Can you just please go
before Gus gets back?
I wanna be here when he gets back.
I want to tell him about us.
So you... you want to ruin this for me?
Yes. I want to tell him about us.
And then, he's gonna leave you,
[stutters] and you and I can get back
to making this work, okay?
[stutters] This is the story
we're gonna tell our kids.
"Your mom was dating a loser,
and I... I came after her.
I chased after her." All right?
This... this guy is a wimp.
He's not gonna fight for you.
You want someone
who is gonna fight for you!
No, Dustin, I don't. Please, I don't.
You don't know
what the fuck you want, okay?
I'm being direct with you.
This fucking guy is not the answer
to your problems, okay?
You need to have the courage
to stay in the game with me
until we figure this out together.
Dustin... just let me go.
Maybe with Gus I can be happy.
[chuckles] You're gonna destroy him.
Maybe I will. Maybe.
But let me figure that out
on my own, okay?
If you love me,
you're gonna give me the space to do that.
[doorknob rattling]
[Gus] Hello? Mickey?
[knocking on door]
-[Gus] Mickey?
-[whispering] Can you--
Can you just go out there, please?
[knocking on door]
[Gus] Mickey?
-Hello?
-[knocks on door]
-You there?
-[Mickey] I'm coming, Gus! Sorry!
Sorry.
-Um...
-Hey, what's up?
Hi, I was in the bathroom
and I locked the door
'cause I didn't want anyone
to be able to get in.
Oh, it's okay. I don't trust anybody
around here. It's fine.
Uh, hope you like Sprite.
Oh, well, I'm...
I'm more of a 7 Up girl, actually.
It's okay. They literally taste the same.
Hey, you okay?
I... I gotta tell you something.
Okay. Let's talk.
Uh, yeah, it's um...
It's... it's kinda scary to say.
Look...
I know I've been coming on strong.
It's just...
I think when I got back,
I just got excited--
No, it's not that.
Gus, it's not. It's...
[sighs]
[stutters] I wanna be
in a relationship with you.
[Beck's "True Love Will Find You
In The End" playing]
-Okay. All right.
-Yeah.
I don't wanna do
any more nonexclusive bullshit.
That ends today.
I wanna really try and work on this
and be in a real adult relationship.
I want that, too.
-Really?
-Of course.
I'm in. Mickey, I'm in.
Let's... let's fucking be a couple.
-Okay, let's... let's be a couple.
-We're a couple.
♪ True love will find you in the end ♪
♪ You'll find out just who... ♪
[Mickey chuckles]
-[Gus] I got you.
-Mmm-hmm.
[balcony door opens]
-♪ Don't be sad, I know you will ♪
-[balcony door closes]
♪ Don't give up until ♪
-♪ True love will find you in the end ♪
-[door opens and closes]
♪ This is a promise with a catch ♪
♪ Only if you're looking
Will it find you ♪
♪ 'Cause true love is searching too ♪
♪ How can it recognize you
Unless you step out into the light? ♪
♪ Don't be sad, I know you will ♪
♪ Don't give up until ♪
♪ True love finds you in the end  ♪
[harmonica playing]
♪ True love will find you in the end ♪